Wh-What?!
Sera! Be my bride!
A dream? Of the barbarian? But why?
What is that sound?
The Warrior Princess and the Barbaric King
Wh-Wh-What are you doing in here?
What are you asking? Why wouldn't
I be sleeping in my bedroom?
Why am I in your bedroom?!
And why are you nude?!
You're making a real fuss
for how early it is.
It's good to see you're so full
of energy, after last night.
What happened last night...?
I don't remember anything,
and I'm not sure I want to!
Did you not just say you
wouldn't force yourself on me?
Come now, let's not quibble over details.
Do not treat a lady's chastity
as some trifle, you animal!
Wait, hold on.
It's bad enough I've been
taken captive by barbarians...
if I were to bear his child,
I'd be giving rise to another
enemy to my homeland!
Kill me! Now!
What sense does that make?
If you wanted to kill me,
I'd understand, but why seek to die?
You would never understand.
The shame of being defeated
and taken captive in battle...
Compounded by the shame of attacking
a nude, unarmed opponent, in a rage...
All these things disgrace
a knight's honor!
So, before I become any
greater of an embarrassment,
I would rather you put
me out of my misery!
Well, that certainly sounds unpleasant.
U-Unpleasant?!
How else would you describe your belief
that shame and embarrassment are
enough to make one yearn for death?
You make light of shame
and embarrassment?!
These things may be of
no concern for you barbarians,
but for a noble lady—
Master Veor.
Your clothes have dried.
You woke up with no trouble.
You're lucky.
What?
After Master Veor returned yesterday...
you had a mild overdose of the sleeping
drugs used to transport you here,
so you suddenly started
vomiting, before collapsing.
You had me quite worried.
I collapsed? Then...
That's what you meant about... last night.
I should apologize. It was administered
in the same dosage that my people use.
It's a type of paralytic poison,
so you were brought to my
room so you could rest.
Paralytic poison?!
It slows the flow of blood,
which makes it good
for helping wounds close, as well.
Then... nothing was done to me?
Other than a misapplication
of medicine, no.
I can't have you dying so soon
after I've decided to wed you!
Don't be so confusing!
Hand me a sword! I need
to beat some sense into you!
Looks like I don't need
to worry about you.
And the breakfast preparations
won't go to waste, either.
Breakfast...?
Yes. You haven't eaten anything in the
day since you left the battlefield.
I'd imagine you're hungry.
I'll be waiting in the other room,
so come along once you've calmed down.
Hey—Wait!
I can't believe that a
knight such as myself
has been given shelter by barbarians...
Grandfather.
I taught you, my granddaughter,
my swordplay since you asked to learn,
and you've proven to be
a bit too talented...
Maybe if you were a man...
or could give up on being a knight...
you might've known some happiness.
Serafina. You've rejected
another marriage proposal.
Wanting to be a knight, as a woman...
how long are you going to
indulge this selfishness?
You've more than established yourself
as a leader of knights at this point.
You need to get married while
there are still viable prospects.
A sword has never changed policy.
Brother...
I sensed a profound
sincerity from your blade.
It was enough that I fell
for you in that moment.
I've paid so little mind to my
femininity, the last thing I need
is to suddenly be desired for it!
No... no, that isn't
the last thing I need.
Considering he's a barbarian,
and I'm a prisoner of war...
That is the entirety of the situation!
And the breakfast for a prisoner of
war is likely to be the bare minimum.
They say the best way to whittle one's
self-respect is through their diet.
But as a knight, I've dealt
with military rations,
so I doubt they can do much worse.
I will display the pride of
the Lavillant clan that was
chosen to be part of
the Eastern Expedition!
There you are, Sera.
Come, have a seat.
There's meat!
Where did this fatty meat come from?
Even at home, something like this...
No, given the state of my homeland,
I never came across such a feast!
I'm not sure what a good portion would
be for a female warrior from the west,
but I'm sure a quarter should suffice.
This is a quarter?!
It's bigger than my torso!
What is this? Why would they
possibly be treating me like this?!
What's the matter? Not hungry?
I see. Your scheme is obvious, now.
Foisting such luxury on me to
winnow away at my knight's pride,
so that you might tame me, is that it?
No matter! I would rather starve to
death than be indulged by barbarians!
Did my stomach really need to
rumble at that exact moment?!
K-Kill me!
Are you fond of saying that?
If your stomach still yearns for food,
it means your body wishes to go on living.
To not eat, in spite of that,
is nothing more than self-deception.
To say nothing of the disrespect
for the life that was lost
so this food could be brought to you.
Taking a life should be a serious
matter, not done out of sport.
Surely, the west isn't so
different in what they believe.
All that aside, stop second-guessing
everything and eat.
It's good!
That smile...
What is it, odd eyes?
I should inform you...
Though Master Veor didn't mention it,
given he took the fact for granted,
this meat was hunted
specifically to welcome you.
A welcome?
On a hunt he went on, by himself,
so that you would have something
fine to eat upon waking.
Master Veor is as capable
as he is famous...
He would be the equivalent of
one of your western royalty.
I mean, if he's the son of some great
chief... that would make him a prince.
Someone like that went to a lot of
effort to show you this hospitality.
Would turning away from it not
be bad manners for a noble?
Fine. It would bring shame to my name
as a knight to reject such efforts.
But if this is some paltry... so tender...
So good!
It's so tender, but so juicy!
There's a bit of gaminess,
but the flavor is good enough,
it comes across as a slight accent!
I doubt even Illdoren royalty
get to eat something like this!
Glorious... too glorious!
Well? Good, isn't it?
Well, I can hardly complain after
being served something like this.
And while I don't intend on marrying you,
this is enough for me to overlook
the matter of my drugging.
That's good, then.
I have to ask, as good as it tastes,
what manner of meat is this?
Care to see?
It was bled and the organs were
removed up in the mountains,
but the rest is being cleaned out back.
If you're curious, you can
look from that window.
I want to know!
If we could domesticate this animal
in my homeland, then maybe...
There's no shortage of
them in these parts.
It's called a dragon.
A-A dragon?!
Th-This is dragon meat?!
Yes.
As in... the legendary...
flying monster?!
That's apparently how
they're viewed in the west.
They're supposed to breathe
fire and have toxic flesh!
Those do exist, but this
is a different breed.
That aside, Sera, I notice
you're... not slowing down.
Well, if it tastes good, it tastes good.
I don't think she intends
on dying any time soon.
I'm allowed to go outside?
Yes. There's something around the
mountain I'd like to show you.
What? You look like the dragon
that swallowed a wasp's nest.
Obviously I can't just trust
you about something like that.
It's a matter of trust?
Of course it is! I've only been
your prisoner for two days!
Not that the length of
time matters, but...
Besides, it doesn't make sense,
waltzing around lands filled
with such bizarre creatures!
You speak of sense, but surely common
sense varies depending on location.
I'd say different creatures and
cultures are a big part of that.
Or is it simply that you're afraid?
I can't deny that you've
baited me into this...
But don't get the wrong idea.
This doesn't mean I trust you people.
Obviously. Still, I get the feeling
you'll take a liking to your surroundings,
once you've seen them.
And what are you basing that on?
There's no basis.
It's just a gut feeling, that's all.
Something wrong?
No... it's just... more bountiful,
and richer in nature than I had imagined.
The battlefields we fought
on were wastelands,
but the life in these lands
has always been strong.
I just hope you don't faint from it all.
D-Don't mock me!
Damned barbarian. The dragon and this
scenery were basically sneak attacks.
I don't know what he
intends on showing me,
but if I can brace for it,
I won't be surprised.
So many animals...
Dragons are just another one of
the inhabitants of these parts.
They're a pain to hunt,
but if you leave their lairs alone,
they don't bother humans.
You make it sound so
simple to get used to!
It will be, once you live here.
You certainly seemed to enjoy
the one you ate this morning.
M-My meat wasn't flying...
It's no different than poultry, then.
What is that sound?
Is that... a waterfall?!
I've never seen one before!
What do you think, Sera?
Not a sight you'd see in the west.
Are you mocking me?
My homeland has its own...
No. It doesn't.
I wasn't trying to brag, mind you.
But I did want you to see it.
Now, then, there's one other
thing that brings us here.
There is?
Yes.
First of all... strip.
Wh-Why would I?!
You ask why?
There's only one thing a man and
woman would do in the water,
without their clothes.
D-Don't tell me...
Bathe.
Do you have to say everything
in such a misleading way?!
Even if I'm getting used to it!
Besides, why would you have
mixed bathing?! It's indecent!
You can call it indecent, but that's
simply how it's done around here.
Don't they say "When in foreign lands,
do as the foreigners do"?
I'm not going to engage with
your barbarian practices!
My, you're a fierce one.
You're beginning to smell a bit.
We don't have bathhouses in our culture.
Wiping you down like
last night can only do so much.
It won't be long before
you start to stink...
I can't believe you, either.
Taking your clothes off with no
hesitation, in front of a man...
On some level, it's just a
matter of being used to it.
Master Veor even went
to a different stream
because of the fuss you were making.
So, I'm here to accompany you.
More like watch me, so I can't run.
No, I'd say it has more to
do with keeping you safe.
My safety?
There are other things out
here, like the sawaiwao.
See?
Don't you "see?" me!
Well, they're all pretty docile
if they can be found here.
You make it sound like we're
surrounded by monsters or something.
Because we are.
How can I bathe while
surrounded by monsters?!
I'm going back!
But that's...
Well, I guess it'll be fine.
I ran off without thinking...
But it was careless to leave my shoes
and clothes in the other direction.
I'm not happy about it, but I
suppose I'll head back and get dressed.
Is someone there?
Oh, no! Someone else is out here!
Kill me!
What'll happen if I run
into a real savage,
unlike the strangely rational Veor?!
S-Stay back!
What are you doing here?
S-So handsome!
A young barbarian warrior?
And one that's so beautiful!
I'm hard-pressed to think of many
men in the west who look so...
Y-You! Stop staring!
From the state of you...
I'd guess some beasts appeared while
you were bathing in the falls.
My mother was a warrior
from the west, too.
I've heard stories like that.
She would tell me, when I was young,
about how there was less nature and
fewer animals where she came from.
From his age, that'd have to have
been in the 16th Expedition...
A lady knight from 20
years ago is his mother?
Damn, I'm actually getting cold.
Wh-What are you doing?
Honestly, a woman shouldn't
risk catching a chill.
Let's head back to where your clothes are.
You can use my coat in the meantime.
What a gentleman!
What is a man who could be a western
knight doing among these barbarians?!
Or is it just Veor, whose first
words to me were about marriage,
that is abnormal?
Are you all right?
Do you have a fever?
Too close! His face is too close!
You're turning red, too.
Not good! I don't have enough experience
with men to know what to do!
This isn't good.
You might have trouble making it
down the mountain.
So be it. I'll have to
touch you, so forgive me.
Wha...?
You're as light as a feather.
What am I supposed to do here?
Even I'm shocked at how
little resistance I can muster...
Okay, let's go.
Oh, I finally found you.
Sorry to ruin what seems
like a nice moment,
but how did this even happen,
Master Veor?
Ve...
What, you didn't realize?
I suppose I didn't get to tidy
myself up before proposing, but...
All it took was a shave for
you to blush like a maiden.
You're an innocent one, aren't you?
I am a maiden, you barbarian!
To slap with such force
from an unstable position.
I knew I liked you for a reason.
You're bright red.
Are you going to be all right?
If I had a sword, it would've
been grounds for a duel!
Besides, this is your fault for
taking me into that den of monsters.
You didn't need to worry about that.
Huh?
Master Veor patrols the areas where
dangerous creatures might appear.
You didn't seem to want any
company while in the nude.
I had intended on protecting you
by your side, at first, but...
Compared to the yoitobari
we had for breakfast,
the inhabitants of the
river are all peaceful.
W-Was that dragon that dangerous?
I wouldn't say so.
They have a wild temper,
but are generally pretty cowardly.
Only you would say that, Master Veor.
Even if they are herbivores, a dragon of
that size is a danger for most people.
I can't argue with that, but...
I got to see another side
of the woman I love today.
It was a small price to pay, frankly.
I will forgive you, this one time!
On account of how nice the scenery was.
But it won't happen again!
That's fine by me!
It's a relief to know how
gracious my wife is, as well.
Wi—?!
You don't get to decide
that I'm your wife!
Really? Still?
Don't give me that look full of pity!
Unbelievable...
What an absolute mess. Although...
I suppose he's easier
on the eyes without that beard.
Only slightly, though!
Days later
But...
Why?
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Lee Francis
Andy Ellis
Zachary Carlysle
Salem Alabanza
Sho Stifler